<infotexts language="English" nowhitespace="false" translatedname="English">
    <!-- Loading Tips -->
    <loadingscreentip>‖color:gui.blue‖More Level Content Tip: ‖end‖Distress beacons won't last forever, they will disapear from the map after some time.</loadingscreentip>
    <loadingscreentip>‖color:gui.blue‖More Level Content Tip: ‖end‖Jump starters can be used to restart shuttles that have run out of power. Some systems (Oxygen generators) should be turned off when jump starting a shuttle, as they use an excessive amount of power.</loadingscreentip>
    <loadingscreentip>‖color:gui.blue‖More Level Content Tip: ‖end‖If you take your time on a distress mission, whoever activated it might be dead by the time you show up.</loadingscreentip>
    <loadingscreentip>‖color:gui.blue‖More Level Content Tip: ‖end‖If you have Dynamic Europa installed, high reputation with the Bandit faction will turn pirate bases passive.</loadingscreentip>
    <loadingscreentip>‖color:gui.blue‖More Level Content Tip: ‖end‖There have been reports of pirate bases using sonar jammers to mask their presence.</loadingscreentip>
    <loadingscreentip>‖color:gui.blue‖More Level Content Tip: ‖end‖Following stange sonar pings may lead to automatic traders, waystations or other structures. Who knows what you could find!</loadingscreentip>
    <loadingscreentip>‖color:gui.blue‖More Level Content Tip: ‖end‖When responding to a distress beacon, submariners may find whoever activated it dead on arrival. All is not lost, however, as if they had a sub it can be salvaged.</loadingscreentip>
    <loadingscreentip>‖color:gui.blue‖More Level Content Tip: ‖end‖Visiting a waystation will often reveal another location on the map.</loadingscreentip>
    <loadingscreentip>‖color:gui.blue‖More Level Content Tip: ‖end‖Relay Stations require basic knowledge of math and the wiring system to complete. When in doubt, ask your nearest engineer.</loadingscreentip>
    <loadingscreentip>‖color:gui.blue‖More Level Content Tip: ‖end‖Created by the Keletco conglomerate, Relay Stations are one of the few remaining creations of it's brief stint on Europa.</loadingscreentip>
    <loadingscreentip>‖color:gui.blue‖More Level Content Tip: ‖end‖Relay stations were superseded by beacon stations, however some outposts still rely on the outdated system. In recent years, many of these stations have broken down due to lack of maintence.</loadingscreentip>

    
    <!-- Distress Ghostship Objective -->
    <dgs.obj.exploreship>Explore at least 50% of the ship.</dgs.obj.exploreship>
    <dgs.obj.optionalsalvage>(OPTIONAL) Salvage the ghostship by bringing it to the end of the level.</dgs.obj.optionalsalvage>
    <dgs.inrageforsalvage>The drifting ghostship is in range for salvage.</dgs.inrageforsalvage>

    <entityname.stomach_acid_vent>Stomach Acid Vent</entityname.stomach_acid_vent>
    <entityname.relaystationsmaintenceguide>Keletco Relay Station Service Manual</entityname.relaystationsmaintenceguide>
    <entitydescription.relaystationsmaintenceguide>A service manual detailing the service and maintence of Keletco brand relay stations, it's well worn and barely held together.</entitydescription.relaystationsmaintenceguide>
    <relaystation.maintenceguide>KELETCO RELAY MAINTENCE GUIDE\n\nGreetings and congratulations on your new employment as a Keletco Service Technician! In your new role as a KST, you'll both be representing the Keletco brand as well as maintaining multiple relay stations on Europa. This is an important role as relay stations are the back bone of Europa's growing trade network. As a KST, you will be exp[???]\n[The rest of the page is too water damaged to read]\n\nTOOLS OF THE TRADE\nIncluded in each Keletco Relay Station is a basic repair kit, consisting of:\n  - 1x Keletco Relay Station Service Manual\n  - 1x Screwdriver\n  - 5x Standard Electrical Wire\n  - 1x Oxygen Mask\n  - 1x Oxygen Tank\n\nIt is expected of each KST to return these supplies to the repair kit after completion of the repair and to restock any used or damaged supplies. Reme[???]\n\nRELAY STATION COMPONENTS\n[???]orking with the relay station it's important to know what each part of t[???]\n\nINPUT RELAY\nLocated by the IN junction box supplies the input voltage of a message. This is then fed into the MODULATION COMPONENTS located throughout the relay station. \n\nMODULATION COMPONENTS\nThese come in sets of 4. Each component in the same set will do the same operation but with a different value. The value they will preform the operation with is displayed on the screen above them. \n\nOUTPUT RELAY\nLocated by the OUT junction box, this relay is what sends the end result of the MODULATION COMPONENTS to the VALIDATION CIRCUIT\n\nVALIDATION CIRCUIT\nLocated by the OUT junction box, the validation circuit will predict what the expected output is and display it on the TRGT screen. It will then set the display light to either red or green, dependingon if the expected voltage was given to it.\n\nREPAIRING A RELAY STATION\n\n[???]nter a damaged relay station, it is important to first go over the calibration terminal. The calibration terminal will display the example inputs and their respective outputs of the damagedsection. Relay stat[???]ration terminal will give you an example of an input voltage, then three values showing the inputs voltage after each modulation step, then finally the output voltage. Each stepmust be done in sequence to assure the correct[???]\n\nYOUR TYPICAL REPAIR\n\n  - Read the calibration terminal\n  - Retrieve the screwdriver, wires and oxygen mask from the Repair Kit\n  - Equip the oxygen mask\n  - Locate the "INPUT" relay, this should be near the "IN" label\n  - Connect one end of a wire to the "SIGNAL_OUT_1" pin of the INPUT relay\n  - Connect the other end of the wire to the "SIGNAL_IN_1" pin of the first\n     modulation component (Use your Keletco Kalculator and the calibration terminal to\n       determine thefirst modulation component)\n  - Connect another wire to the output pin of the first modulation component\n  - Connect the other end of the wire to the input of the second modulation component\n  - Continue until you've completed all 4 steps in the sequence\n  - Wire the output of the final modulation component to the "SIGNAL_IN_1" pin of the\n      OUT relay\n\nIf you have followed the above steps correctly, the validation circuit should now be flashing green. A hearty Keletco congratulations on completing your first of many relay repairs! \n\n(If the validation circuit is NOT flashing green, consult the calibration terminal and repeat these steps. You have made an error somewhere)\n\nSAFTY AND YOU\n\nEuropa is a dangerous place! While Keletco has taken steps to ensure your safety while repairing a relay station, some of the burden rests on yourself. Thus it is important for any Keletco ServiceTechnician to follo[???]\n[The rest of the pages are stuck together]</relaystation.maintenceguide>

</infotexts>