<infotexts language="English" nowhitespace="false" translatedname="English">
    <!-- Updated texts -->
    <entitydescription.jumpstarter>Battery powered electrical device used to jump start dead systems.\n‖color:gui.blue‖Use to restart stranded shuttles during distress missions, can be reused.‖end‖</entitydescription.jumpstarter>
    <entitydescription.captains_notebook>A small, wellworn paper book. Typically used by sub captains to record their travels.\n‖color:gui.blue‖Can be sold for a high price at outposts or read to garner some experience.‖end‖</entitydescription.captains_notebook>
    
    <loadingscreentip>‖color:gui.blue‖More Level Content Tip: ‖end‖If you have ‖color:gui.green‖Dynamic Europa‖end‖ installed, high reputation with the Bandit faction will turn pirate bases passive.</loadingscreentip>


    <!-- Pirate Items -->
    <entityname.mlcpirateradio>‖color:gui.Orange‖Pirate Radio‖end‖</entityname.mlcpirateradio>
    <entitydescription.mlcpirateradio>A rugged, custom built radio. Used by pirates to announce their presence to each other.\n‖color:gui.green‖You could use this to negotiate safe passage if there's a pirate base in the area,‖end‖ ‖color:gui.red‖for a price.‖end‖\n‖color:gui.blue‖Can be sold for a very high price to military outposts.‖end‖</entitydescription.mlcpirateradio>

    <!-- New Loading Tips -->
    <loadingscreentip>‖color:gui.blue‖More Level Content Tip: ‖end‖If you have ‖color:gui.green‖Dynamic Europa‖end‖ installed, you may find a Pirate Radio during your travels. Depending on your reputation with the bandit faction, the options this radio gives to you will change.</loadingscreentip>

    <!-- Campaign map update texts -->
    <mapupdate.generic.header>Campaign Map Updated</mapupdate.generic.header>   
    <mapupdate.piratebase.revealed>A pirate base between [location1] and [location2] has been revealed!</mapupdate.piratebase.revealed>
    <mapupdate.unknown.revealed>A location of interest has been revealed!</mapupdate.unknown.revealed>

    <!-- Maps -->
    <entityname.mlc-blankmap>Blank Map</entityname.mlc-blankmap>
    <entitydescription.mlc-blankmap>Looking closer it's blanker than blank. It's totally empty. The longer you stare the emptier it gets. Your hands feel empty, your heart feels empty, you feel... Using this would be a bad idea, you should put this back where you found it as fast as possible.</entitydescription.mlc-blankmap>

    <entityname.mlc-map>Cavern Map</entityname.mlc-map>
    <entitydescription.mlc-map>A worn map of the local caverns and water ways.\nIt's a bit old but there might be some identifiable features on it to those familiar with the area.</entitydescription.mlc-map>

    <entityname.mlc-piratebasemap>Esoteric Map</entityname.mlc-piratebasemap>
    <entitydescription.mlc-piratemap>A map written in pirate code.\nIt's hard to decypher but those in the know might have more luck.\n‖color:gui.blue‖Military outposts would be very interested in this.‖end‖</entitydescription.mlc-piratemap>

    <entityname.mlc-treasuremap>‖color:gui.Orange‖Treasure Map‖end‖</entityname.mlc-treasuremap>
    <entitydescription.mlc-treasuremap>This is very clearly a treasure map, dotted line and red X included.\nWhat are you waiting for? It's time to find some sunken treasure!</entitydescription.mlc-treasuremap>

    <entityname.mlc-unknownmap>‖color:gui.Orange‖Unlabled Map‖end‖</entityname.mlc-unknownmap>
    <entitydescription.mlc-unknownmap>A detailed map in exelent condition. Anyone could read this with ease.\nFor all the care that went into making this map the creator has neglected to note what it actually leads to... But that doesn't matter, right?</entitydescription.mlc-unknownmap>

    <entityname.mlc-mapframe>Map Frame</entityname.mlc-mapframe>
    <entitydescription.mlc-mapframe>A framing device used by captains to organize map fragments and plot routes.</entitydescription.mlc-mapframe>
</infotexts>