<infotexts language="English" nowhitespace="false" translatedname="English">
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.c1>The look of relief on the captains face is palpable. "Oh thank Jove,
        someone actually came! I was beginning to think we'd have to make a swim for it.", He lets
        out a stress filled chuckle.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.c1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1>"What happened?"</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1>

    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.c1>The captain paces restlessly, he walks with a noticable limp. He
        flinches slightly every time his foot hits the floor. "Dan, my previous engineer, got mauled
        by mudraptors, Jove rest his soul. Now I'm not one to fiddle with electronics and after my
        mechanic almost shocked himself to death I knew we had to hire another one." He rests a hand
        on his hip, "So we hired a new one at the outpost we'd docked to. It wasn't until we were
        underway that I found out I'd hired one of those honkmother clowns."</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.c1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.c2>"We're not even a week out of port when we got jumped by a swarm
        of crawlers. During the chaos I hear a single bike horn honk and all the lights go out. When
        we finally got the situation under control, we found out our new engineer was gone." The
        captain collapses into his chair, clearly tired and possibly reconsidering his career
        choices. "As well as all our fuel rods."</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.c2>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.c3>"That's the last time I'm letting a big-shoe on my boat.." The
        captain glances up from you, he looks small in his chair. "You.. You wouldn't happen to have
        a fuel rod to spare?"</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.c3>

    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1>"I'll see what I can do."</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.c1>A twinge of hope fills the captains weary eyes. "You're a
        saint, you know that?"</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.c1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.c2>"O-Oh, you're back. I was starting to think.. Well- uh, ha ha,
        you're here now anyway."</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.c2>

    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1>I'll be back.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1>

    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.c1>"You have the rod yet?"</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.c1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o1>"Not Yet."</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o2>"Yes, here you go." [+Location Rep]</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o2>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3>"We might have a spare, if you throw in some marks for my
        efforts." [Helm: HARD]</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3>

    <!-- Intimidation success -->
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1>"I- I.." He pauses, his leg begins jiggle up and down.
        "Here, this is everything I've got. Please."</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1>"I'll see if I can find a rod."</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1>

    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1>The captain has shrunk back into his seat. He
        doesn't meet your gaze as a sense of shame fills the air. What a sad, little man.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o1>...</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2>Give him the rod.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1>You toss the rod at him and he doesn't move
        to grab it. It clatters loudly to the floor loudly, echoing in the empty sub.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1.o1>Whatever.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1.o1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1.o2>"Well? You paid good money for that,
        aren't you going to use it?"</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1.o2>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1.o2.c1>The captain is eerily still, his body
        limp in a chair too big for him. You turn to leave before he suddenly blurts out, "When I
        was a kid, me and Dan would always watch the subs leaving Meltwater. Even if you weren't
        near a porthole, you could hear them through the walls if you got your ear close enough. If
        you really strained, you could almost fool yourself into thinking you could hear a moloch
        herd." He goes silent, seemingly lost in though. "D-Do you think, if- If I submerged my
        head.. Would I hear the molochs?"</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1.o2.c1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1.o2.c1.o1>Walk Away</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1.o2.c1.o1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1.o2.c1.o2>"Sure."</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1.o2.c1.o2>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1.o2.c1.o2.c1>He gives you a weak smile, his
        eyes focusing on you again. "It's a nice thought, t-to hold onto anyways.." He's completly
        off his rocker.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1.o2.c1.o2.c1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1.o2.c1.o2.c1.o1>Time to leave.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1.o2.c1.o2.c1.o1>

    <!-- Intimidation failure -->
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c2>"..F-Fuck you! Do you just, just go answering peoples
        distress calls to extort them? You're no saint! You're the wolf in sheep's clothing, the
        devil offering me a hand with a knife behind his back! Your heart is cold as the ice sheets,
        your heart as black as the abyss! You'll get exactly what you deserve, the only thing you
        deserve!"</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c2>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c2.o1>Uh oh.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c2.o1>

    <!-- High clown rep -->
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>Before you hand over the rod you pause. You hear a faint
        whisper, in the back of your mind. "This man is down in the dumps, you shouldn't just give
        him the rod, you should also cheer him up! Everyone loves surprises, what better way to
        lighten his day!"</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>Good point voice. [+Clown Rep]</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>Before you hand over the fuel rod, you decide to rig
        a surprise for the captain when he puts it into the reactor. An unseen force guides your
        hands as you deftly sabotage the fuel rod.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1.o1>This should brighten his day! You get the
        premonition you should leave before he puts it into the reactor.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1.o1>

    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2>Not today voice. [+Location Rep]</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2>

    <!-- Refuse -->
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o2>"Sorry, but we can't spare any."</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o2>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o2.c1>"N-No!" A manic look fills his eyes, you notice his hand
        reaching for his revolver as his whole body tenses.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o2.c1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o2.c1.o1>"Don't try it." [Weapons: HARD]</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o2.c1.o1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o2.c1.o1.c1>He collapses back into the chair, defeated. "Maybe..
        Maybe the next sub will help us?" He lets out a weak laugh before staring at the wall behind
        you, a blank expression on his face.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o2.c1.o1.c1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o2.c1.o1.c1.o1>You're not a charity, he chose this life.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o2.c1.o1.c1.o1>

    <!-- Loop back to main -->
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o2.c1.o2>"Actually, we might have a spare. I'll have to check."</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o2.c1.o2>

    <!-- End Text -->
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.end>The captain thanks you for the rod and heads to stick it into the
        reactor.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.end>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.end.o1>Looks like your job here is done.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.end.o1>

    <!-- AutoTrader Overdose -->
    <MapFeature.autotraderoverdose.c1>The mechanic shakes their whole body, "Whooo man, I steped out
        there for a hot minute! But, but you man. You brought me back right? Hell yeah man! That's
        what I'm about!" They pause and look around, "Hey man, you're from that sub that's docked
        below right? Y-You need another crew member? I'm the best!"</MapFeature.autotraderoverdose.c1>
    <MapFeature.autotraderoverdose.o1>Welcome board.</MapFeature.autotraderoverdose.o1>
    <MapFeature.autotraderoverdose.o1.c1>"You won't regret it man, ha ha!" They seem excited.</MapFeature.autotraderoverdose.o1.c1>
    <MapFeature.autotraderoverdose.o2>No thank you.</MapFeature.autotraderoverdose.o2>
    <MapFeature.autotraderoverdose.o2.c1>"Oh, oh.. Oh well, I-I guess, I'll just. Wait for the next
        crew, right man? Someone'll pick me up, yeah!"</MapFeature.autotraderoverdose.o2.c1>

    <!-- Abyss Research -->
    <MapFeature.abyssresearch.c1>As you walk past the researcher the look up at you. "Oh good you're here, finally. This is very important, make sure it arrives in once piece. They shove a bundle of papers into your arms. You try to explain you're not a mailman but they've already tuned you out. Looks like there's a location scribbled onto the front of the packet.</MapFeature.abyssresearch.c1>
    
    <MapFeature.mailman.impatient>There's an impatient looking researcher here.</MapFeature.mailman.impatient>
    <MapFeature.mailman.waiting>Waiting for something?</MapFeature.mailman.waiting>
    <MapFeature.mailman.exposition>He turns to look at you. "Yes, actually. A devlivery crew was supposed to deliver some important research from a colleague of mine yesterday but they've been a no-show so far. I'm begining to think an abyss creature got them."</MapFeature.mailman.exposition>
    <MapFeature.mailman.handover>Hand over research data.</MapFeature.mailman.handover>
    <MapFeature.mailman.later>Later.</MapFeature.mailman.later>
    <MapFeature.mailman.missing>Where did you leave that research data again?</MapFeature.mailman.missing>
    <MapFeature.mailman.snatch>He snatches the bundle of paper from your hands and begins to franticly read it. "Aha! Ha HA! This is it! This IS IT! So much to go through and so little time..." He turns to walk away.</MapFeature.mailman.snatch>
    <MapFeature.mailman.payment>*cough* About my payment...</MapFeature.mailman.payment>
    <MapFeature.mailman.groan>He lets out a groan before turning back around, "You submariners, always wanting to get paid for your work, as if labor to further humanity isn't a reward in itself! I suppose you want marks, although.." He looks around, as if to see if anyone is listening. Seemingly satisfied, he leans in close, "I could also part ways with whatever's in this mystery box..</MapFeature.mailman.groan>
    <MapFeature.mailman.box>Mystery box! Mystery box!</MapFeature.mailman.box>
    <MapFeature.mailman.sucker>With a florish he produces a strange box shaped object, before abruptly shoving it into your arms. "It's your problem now sucker!!" He yells out before running away.</MapFeature.mailman.sucker>
    <MapFeature.mailman.marks>Marks for me, please.</MapFeature.mailman.marks>
    <MapFeature.mailman.lame>"No sense of adventure! Bah, here's your marks. I've got work to do!"</MapFeature.mailman.lame>
    <MapFeature.mailman.wasteoftime>What a colossal waste of time.</MapFeature.mailman.wasteoftime>

    <EventText.clownstation_preformanceofalifetime.c1>The preformer looks up from their papers. "Oh hello! You must be here for the show!" They bounce up and down slightly.</EventText.clownstation_preformanceofalifetime.c1>
    <EventText.clownstation_preformanceofalifetime.o1>Show? What show?</EventText.clownstation_preformanceofalifetime.o1>
    <EventText.clownstation_preformanceofalifetime.o1.c1>"Oh, surely you've heard about it!" They dramatically lean backwards, "The famous clown Pagliacci is here to give the preformance of a life time!" They jump up into a ta-da pose. "Free for all to see, as is his wish." They look at you, expectantly.</EventText.clownstation_preformanceofalifetime.o1.c1>
    <EventText.clownstation_preformanceofalifetime.o1.o1>I'm interested.</EventText.clownstation_preformanceofalifetime.o1.o1>
    <EventText.clownstation_preformanceofalifetime.o1.o1.c1>"Perfect! Head down to the theatre and get ready for a show!" They giggle to themselves. Typical clown.</EventText.clownstation_preformanceofalifetime.o1.o1.c1>
    <EventText.clownstation_preformanceofalifetime.o1.o2>I've got no time for clowns.</EventText.clownstation_preformanceofalifetime.o1.o2>
    <EventText.clownstation_preformanceofalifetime.o1.o2.c1>"Such a shame, everyone should take time to enjoy themselves, even you!" Was that a hint of distain in their voice? You must have imagined it.</EventText.clownstation_preformanceofalifetime.o1.o2.c1>
    <EventText.clownstation_preformanceofalifetime.c2>The lights dim as a hidden annoucer proclaims, "And now, please give a warm welcome to Pagliacci!"</EventText.clownstation_preformanceofalifetime.c2>
    <EventText.clownstation_preformanceofalifetime.c3>Where did that cheer come from? You look around for hidden speakers before the clown starts speaking, "Hello, hello everyone! Thank you for such a warm welcome!" He bows, "I remind audience members to keep well away from me while I preform!"</EventText.clownstation_preformanceofalifetime.c3>
    <EventText.clownstation_preformanceofalifetime.c4>"And now, without further delay... My preformance of a life time!"</EventText.clownstation_preformanceofalifetime.c4>
    
    <EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.c1>As you aproach the door, you can hear a heated conversaion on the other side.</EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.c1>
    <EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.c2>"You're nuts! You'll get us both KILLED one of these days messing around with these things with no saftey precautions!".</EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.c2>
    <EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.c3>"You're just jealous the institute mentioned ME by name!" Another voice snears.</EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.c3>
    <EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.c4>"That.. That has nothing to do with it! The institute clearly gave it to us because they didn't want to test it on an outpost and now you're just touching it with your bare hands!"</EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.c4>
    <EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.c5>"And that's why they addressed me by name and not you. Now shut up and help me with this next experiment, I think if I-"</EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.c5>

    <EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.c6>The guard looks concerned. "You heard that sound too, right? Where are the researchers?" They look around the lab, grasping for anything that might give them a hint of the researchers location.</EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.c6>
    <EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.o1>I think they vanished.</EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.o1>
    <EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.o1.c1>"Ah shit, this is the second time this month." The guard sizes you up. "You're a submariner, right? How would you be here otherwise, ha. I had the new batch of researchers equipped with tracking beacons in case it happened again. Would you be willing to recover whatever's left of them?"</EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.o1.c1>
    <EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.o1.o1>Sure, why not.</EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.o1.o1>
    <EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.o1.o1.c1>"Perfect! Here, I'll activate the beacons." The guard takes out a small device from their belt and pressed a button on it. 'You should be able to see the beacons on your sonar now. Once you find them, grab anything that looks, uh, alien-y I guess and brind it back here. I'll be sure to make it worth your time."</EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.o1.o1.c1>
    <EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.o1.o2>Sorry, we're busy already.</EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.o1.o2>
    <EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.o1.o2.c1>"Oh well, it never hurts to ask." The guard looks around the research lab, "The institude is going to be pissed to hear we lost more researchers..." They mutter under their breath.</EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.o1.o2.c1>
    <EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.c7>"Did you find whatever they were messing with?"</EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.c7>
    <EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.o2>Hand over device.</EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.o2>
    <EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.o2.c1>Where did we put that alien object again?</EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.o2.c1>
    <EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.o2.c2>"Ah, perfect! I'll store this somewhere safe." The guard slots the device into a strange looking box on their belt. "Oh, and your reward! The researchers have got some trinkets here if you want them or I could give you some marks."</EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.o2.c2>
    <EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.o2.o1>We'll take the marks.</EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.o2.o1>
    <EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.o2.o2>We'll go for the trinkets.</EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.o2.o2>
    <EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.o3>Not yet.</EventText.abyssresearch_teleportmishap.o3>
    
    <EventText.waystation_revealresearch.c1>The researcher sizes you up, "Hey, you look like a submariner. I've got some colleagues researching the abyss I've been trying to contact. Could you pay them a vist to see if they need anything?"</EventText.waystation_revealresearch.c1>
    <EventText.waystation_revealresearch.o1>Sure, where are they?</EventText.waystation_revealresearch.o1>
    <EventText.waystation_revealresearch.o1.c1>Here, I'll give you the coordinates.</EventText.waystation_revealresearch.o1.c1>
    <EventText.waystation_revealresearch.o2>Do I look like an erran boy?</EventText.waystation_revealresearch.o2>
    <EventText.waystation_revealresearch.o2.c1>The researcher groans, "Your type are usually all too happy to do tasks. Maybe at the next outpost I'll be able to find some real help."</EventText.waystation_revealresearch.o2.c1>

    <EventText.waystation_husk.c1>"There's no way I'm coming out of here until those husks and jove forsaken cultists are dead!" The outpost manager shouts through the door.</EventText.waystation_husk.c1>
    <EventText.waystation_husk.c2>You knock on the door and let the manager know the coast is clear, "They're all dead? Here, let me get the door."</EventText.waystation_husk.c2>
    <EventText.waystation_husk.c3>"I knew we should have kicked those cultists out the airlock the second they came on board" The manager kicks the wall, "Here's something for your trouble. Now I need to make some calls..."</EventText.waystation_husk.c3>
    
    <EventText.waystation_revealtheatre.c1>An ad catches your eye, "Europa got you down? The depths not treating you well? Looking for some jovial fun? Come relax and catch a show! We're ALWAYS open." There's coordinates to a clown theatre attached.</EventText.waystation_revealtheatre.c1>
    
    <EventText.waystation_cargoad.c1>There's an ad here, "Looking for freelancers to transport cargo. More information provided on site." Followed by directions to a nearby outpost.</EventText.waystation_cargoad.c1>

    <EventText.huskchurch_unlockescort.c1>"Welcome to our humble church traveler." You swear you hear a clicking sound whne they talk,  "Say, you look like the type that would help the church. We've got some acolytes on a nearby outpost looking for transport. Here, I'll mark it down for you."</EventText.huskchurch_unlockescort.c1>
    <EventText.huskchurch_cargo.c1>"Welcome to our humble church traveler." You can hear the smile in their voice, it makes you shiver,  "Say, you look like the type that would help the church. We've got some... goods on a nearby outpost looking for transport. Here, I'll mark it down for you. Those that help the church in turn help themselves."</EventText.huskchurch_cargo.c1>
    
    <EventText.clownstation_unlockescort.c1>"You look like a jovial fella, I've got some other jovial friends looking for transport, if you're interested. I'll mark it on your map."</EventText.clownstation_unlockescort.c1>
    <EventText.clownstation_unlockwreck.c1>"You look like a jovial fella, we recently lost some supplies. If you could get them back, you'd be helping us spread the fun. I'll mark it on your map."</EventText.clownstation_unlockwreck.c1>

</infotexts>