<infotexts language="English" nowhitespace="false" translatedname="English">
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.c1>The look of relief on the captains face is palpable. "Oh thank Jove,
        someone actually came! I was beginning to think we'd have to make a swim for it.", He lets
        out a stress filled chuckle.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.c1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1>"What happened?"</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1>

    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.c1>The captain paces restlessly, he walks with a noticable limp. He
        flinches slightly every time his foot hits the floor. "Dan, my previous engineer, got mauled
        by mudraptors, Jove rest his soul. Now I'm not one to fiddle with electronics and after my
        mechanic almost shocked himself to death I knew we had to hire another one." He rests a hand
        on his hip, "So we hired a new one at the outpost we'd docked to. It wasn't until we were
        underway that I found out I'd hired one of those honkmother clowns."</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.c1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.c2>"We're not even a week out of port when we got jumped by a swarm
        of crawlers. During the chaos I hear a single bike horn honk and all the lights go out. When
        we finally got the situation under control, we found out our new engineer was gone." The
        captain collapses into his chair, clearly tired and possibly reconsidering his career
        choices. "As well as all our fuel rods."</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.c2>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.c3>"That's the last time I'm letting a big-shoe on my boat.." The
        captain glances up from you, he looks small in his chair. "You.. You wouldn't happen to have
        a fuel rod to spare?"</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.c3>

    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1>"I'll see what I can do."</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.c1>A twinge of hope fills the captains weary eyes. "You're a
        saint, you know that?"</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.c1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.c2>"O-Oh, you're back. I was starting to think.. Well- uh, ha ha,
        you're here now anyway."</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.c2>

    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1>I'll be back.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1>

    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.c1>"You have the rod yet?"</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.c1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o1>"Not Yet."</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o2>"Yes, here you go." [+Location Rep]</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o2>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3>"We might have a spare, if you throw in some marks for my
        efforts." [Helm: HARD]</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3>

    <!-- Intimidation success -->
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1>"I- I.." He pauses, his leg begins jiggle up and down.
        "Here, this is everything I've got. Please."</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1>"I'll see if I can find a rod."</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1>

    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1>The captain has shrunk back into his seat. He
        doesn't meet your gaze as a sense of shame fills the air. What a sad, little man.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o1>...</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2>Give him the rod.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1>You toss the rod at him and he doesn't move
        to grab it. It clatters loudly to the floor loudly, echoing in the empty sub.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1.o1>Whatever.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1.o1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1.o2>"Well? You paid good money for that,
        aren't you going to use it?"</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1.o2>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1.o2.c1>The captain is eerily still, his body
        limp in a chair too big for him. You turn to leave before he suddenly blurts out, "When I
        was a kid, me and Dan would always watch the subs leaving Meltwater. Even if you weren't
        near a porthole, you could hear them through the walls if you got your ear close enough. If
        you really strained, you could almost fool yourself into thinking you could hear a moloch
        herd." He goes silent, seemingly lost in though. "D-Do you think, if- If I submerged my
        head.. Would I hear the molochs?"</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1.o2.c1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1.o2.c1.o1>Walk Away</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1.o2.c1.o1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1.o2.c1.o2>"Sure."</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1.o2.c1.o2>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1.o2.c1.o2.c1>He gives you a weak smile, his
        eyes focusing on you again. "It's a nice thought, t-to hold onto anyways.." He's completly
        off his rocker.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1.o2.c1.o2.c1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1.o2.c1.o2.c1.o1>Time to leave.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1.o1.c1.o2.c1.o2.c1.o2.c1.o1>

    <!-- Intimidation failure -->
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c2>"..F-Fuck you! Do you just, just go answering peoples
        distress calls to extort them? You're no saint! You're the wolf in sheep's clothing, the
        devil offering me a hand with a knife behind his back! Your heart is cold as the ice sheets,
        your heart as black as the abyss! You'll get exactly what you deserve, the only thing you
        deserve!"</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c2>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c2.o1>Uh oh.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o3.c2.o1>

    <!-- High clown rep -->
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>Before you hand over the rod you pause. You hear a faint
        whisper, in the back of your mind. "This man is down in the dumps, you shouldn't just give
        him the rod, you should also cheer him up! Everyone loves surprises, what better way to
        lighten his day!"</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>Good point voice. [+Clown Rep]</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>Before you hand over the fuel rod, you decide to rig
        a surprise for the captain when he puts it into the reactor. An unseen force guides your
        hands as you deftly sabotage the fuel rod.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1.o1>This should brighten his day! You get the
        premonition you should leave before he puts it into the reactor.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1.o1>

    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2>Not today voice. [+Location Rep]</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2>

    <!-- Refuse -->
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o2>"Sorry, but we can't spare any."</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o2>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o2.c1>"N-No!" A manic look fills his eyes, you notice his hand
        reaching for his revolver as his whole body tenses.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o2.c1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o2.c1.o1>"Don't try it." [Weapons: HARD]</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o2.c1.o1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o2.c1.o1.c1>He collapses back into the chair, defeated. "Maybe..
        Maybe the next sub will help us?" He lets out a weak laugh before staring at the wall behind
        you, a blank expression on his face.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o2.c1.o1.c1>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o2.c1.o1.c1.o1>You're not a charity, he chose this life.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o2.c1.o1.c1.o1>

    <!-- Loop back to main -->
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o2.c1.o2>"Actually, we might have a spare. I'll have to check."</DistressEvent.outoffuel.o1.o2.c1.o2>

    <!-- End Text -->
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.end>The captain thanks you for the rod and heads to stick it into the
        reactor.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.end>
    <DistressEvent.outoffuel.end.o1>Looks like your job here is done.</DistressEvent.outoffuel.end.o1>

    <!-- AutoTrader Overdose -->
    <MapFeature.autotraderoverdose.c1>The mechanic shakes their whole body, "Whooo man, I steped out
        there for a hot minute! But, but you man. You brought me back right? Hell yeah man! That's
        what I'm about!" They pause and look around, "Hey man, you're from that sub that's docked
        below right? Y-You need another crew member? I'm the best!"</MapFeature.autotraderoverdose.c1>
    <MapFeature.autotraderoverdose.o1>Welcome board.</MapFeature.autotraderoverdose.o1>
    <MapFeature.autotraderoverdose.o1.c1>"You won't regret it man, ha ha!" They seem excited.</MapFeature.autotraderoverdose.o1.c1>
    <MapFeature.autotraderoverdose.o2>No thank you.</MapFeature.autotraderoverdose.o2>
    <MapFeature.autotraderoverdose.o2.c1>"Oh, oh.. Oh well, I-I guess, I'll just. Wait for the next
        crew, right man? Someone'll pick me up, yeah!"</MapFeature.autotraderoverdose.o2.c1>
</infotexts>